perfectweddingguide.com 2008-05-12

# Atlanta Weddings

**Privacy Policy**

PWG Holdings, LLC. is committed to your right to privacy. We are constantly making changes as technology advances to ensure that your personal and financial information remains secure. This Privacy Policy serves to inform you, the user, of our practices as they apply to the usage of any collected personal information. We will only use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
**_. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ._**

YOUR CONSENT **  
** By using our web site and/or providing information, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy (established on June 21, 2002.) Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this.   Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We will not knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with any of our sites or to provide any other personally identifying information.  The Internet contains information and material that may be inappropriate or offensive to children. We strongly recommend that you supervise and monitor your children's use of the Internet.  
**_. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ._**

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
**General. PWG Holdings, LLC., as well as its affiliates and advertisers, collect personal information necessary to respond to your requests for products and services and to allow you to use the resources and features available on our web site, including the creation and maintenance of a Free Subscription account and Honeymoon Giveaway contest entry. Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, physical address, e-mail address, phone numbers, age and any other information that identifies or, when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. PWG Holdings, LLC., as well as its affiliates and advertisers, also collect information related to your wedding, including dates and places of the rehearsal, wedding and reception, name of your fiancé, annual income and wedding budget, number of wedding guests, and information relating to your gift registry and honeymoon. PWG Holdings, LLC. also uses order forms for you to request certain information, products and services. On such order forms, we collect your contact information, financial information and demographic information. 

We may also collect information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL.  As you browse our site, we may gather navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, and to comply with any requirements of law. 

Contest. PWG Holdings, LLC., as well as its affiliates and advertisers, frequently sponsor contests to give you the opportunity to win great prizes. Your participation in these contests is optional. Information we collect for such contests can include contact information and demographic information.

Cookies. "Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in several ways. Cookie files are used to tell us whether you have visited our web site previously, and to help us determine whether you came to our web site from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. Cookies can also be used to help you to save and retrieve passwords and other information and preferences you use on our web site, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon each return visit to our web site. Cookies cannot and will not be used by us to retrieve any personal information about you from your computer that you have not previously and voluntarily provided to us. However, cookies may also be received when you link to our affiliates’ and/or advertisers’ sites and we do not have control over how they use this information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. However, most of our features will not function if you do not accept cookies. For more information on cookies, see please refer to your web browser’s help file. 

Forums and message boards. We make forums and message boards available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information, just as full name, address, phone numbers, etc. 

Security. Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information.  Security, Intrusion, and Detection for site security purposes, and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, all traffic is monitored in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage or conduct criminal activity. To protect this web site from unauthorized use and to ensure that it is functioning properly, all users are subject to having all of their activities monitored and recorded by authorized personnel. Anyone using this web site expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that if there is evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, the results of this monitoring shall be made available to appropriate officials for possible prosecution. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to this web site, are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under applicable Federal law.  
**_. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ._**

**WHO YOUR INFORMATION IS SHARED WITH AND HOW IT IS USED  
**When you provide information to PWG Holdings, LLC., the information is stored in our databases. Such information is used by PWG Holdings, LLC. in accordance with this Privacy Policy and by our affiliates and advertisers in accordance with their policies. Information we collect is used to tailor your experience at our site (including the creation of an online bridal registry), to show you content that we think you might be interested in, and to display the content according to your preferences. We also use your personal information to send you information and promotional materials on us and some of our affiliates and/or advertisers. Your contact information may also be used if it becomes necessary to contact you. 

To allow you to use some of our features (including online bridal registry), information we collect will be shared with our affiliates and/or advertisers. Information collected by us, our affiliates or advertisers (for example, when you link to their sites or call a phone number provided by us) will also be shared with third parties, such as product suppliers and wedding professionals, to ensure the successful fulfillment of your product orders or to offer assistance with your wedding. 

Any information we collect may be shared from time to time with a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market research surveys and contest entry processing, and we will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. Contest participation is entirely optional and the information we provide to such third parties will be protected by a confidentiality agreement that will obligate the third party to only use such information to complete the assigned project. 

In addition to the circumstances outlined above, we may disclose your information if required by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary or advisable, including (without limitation) when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.   
**_. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ._**

**THE CHOICES YOU HAVE ABOUT THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION  
**As a user, customer, or contest entrant you will occasionally receive e-mail updates from us about important functionality changes, special offers from us, our affiliates and advertisers, and new PWG Holdings, LLC. services. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, you can “opt-out” anytime by following the link found at the bottom of the update e-mail or the bottom of this page. Our web site also provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications from us, our affiliates or advertisers at the point where we request information from you. In other words, if you don't want us, our affiliates or advertisers to send you e-mails about our or their business, just let us know by marking “No” where appropriate on the form. Please note, however, that PWG Holdings, LLC. reserves the right to limit registration to those who will accept e-mails and to those who will provide the requested information. 

Additional information about online privacy and changes to our policy

Please be aware that on our site we have advertisements and links to other web sites that may collect personal information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of such web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all such web sites, as their policies may be different from our Privacy Policy. Changes in the way we use personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. However, you may always address your concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices to our Corporate office at Corp@pwg.com. Please reference the Privacy Policy in the subject line of your e-mail.  
**_. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ._**

**HEADQUARTERS**  
PWG Holdings, LLC.  
39 Skyline Dr., Ste. 1001  
Lake Mary, FL 32746  
**PHONE:         **(888) 222-7433  
**FAX:**           (888) 933-3404  
**WEB SITE:   **[www.perfectweddingguide.com](http://www.perfectweddingguide.com/)  
**EMAIL** **:**       [corp@pwg.com](mailto:corp@pwg.com)  
**_. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ._**

OPT-OUT **  
** As set forth above, you may opt-out of receiving communications from our partners, and from us, by the following means although you will no longer be provided with services related to your wedding and related services:

_(1) Send an e-mail requesting that you be opted out to[ unsubscribe@pwg.com](mailto:unsubscribe@pwg.com).  Please use the phrase Privacy Page/Opt Out in the subject line._

_(2) Click the following link if you no longer wish to let us collect or use identifiable information about you (you must exist in our database in order to opt out): **Unsubscribe**_

_(3) Click the appropriate link at the bottom of any update e-mails you may receive._[  
](mailto:corp@thepwg.com)
